原翻g  pZ字幕
最新Bd海外影∠螺d
登 www.YYeTs.com
H供交流W  禁止商用盈利
翻g     小酸奶
校     小酸奶
rgS     ]有影子  大[  紫夏
后期     吉吉
O     小酸奶
深入黑暗
第一季第二集
感恩快
Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving!
_斯  H鄣  要我砬
Rose, honey, want me to carve that?
亨利  H鄣  如果我你砬
Henry, my love, if I let you carve,
我到明天都吃不上
we won't eat until tomorrow.
我喜g一切非常精_
I like things to be, you know, precise.
是的  但我F在就I了
Yes, but we're hungry now.
-  金  -  我I了  爸爸
- Isn't that right, Kim? - Yeah. Hungry now, Dad.
切  我能吃
Mom carves, we eat.
血c肉
你切  我只能等
You carve, we wait.
好吧  野U人
All right, savages.
想得美
Yeah, nice try.
今天是感恩
So, this being Thanksgiving,
不如我J真一c
I say we get real
分享我每人想要感恩的|西
and share something that each of us is thankful for.
你先  _斯
You go first, Rose.
我非常感恩我每天在不怎么友好的天空上
I am thankful that I have you two to come home to
辛苦工作  w回家后有你等著我
after the nutjobs I deal with across the not-so-friendly skies.
你的笑一切不_心消云散
Your smiling faces make everything okay.
你呢  小金
How about you, Kimmy?
@一切
For this.
我
For us.
-好吧  爸爸  到你了  -到你了
- All right Dad, your turn. - Yeah, your turn.
好我不用切火u
Well, I'm just thankful I didn't have to carve the turkey
因槲业亩亲庸竟窘辛
'cause my stomach's grumbling.
看
See?
但主要碚f
But mostly, in all honesty,
我不想失去你
I just would never want to lose you two.
你是我一生的
You're the loves of my life.
干杯
Cheers to that.
勰
Love you.
感恩快
Happy Thanksgiving.
抱歉  不是有意你的
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
我要出去了  你吃了
I'm off. You take your meds?
拜托  金伯利
Come on, Kimberly.
我不喜g吃的感X
I don't like the way they make me feel.
}在于  它能椭你
The problem is, they're helping.
把手伸出
Give me your paw.
乖
Good girl.
我知道你今天不想好好c祝
I know you don't want to make a big deal out of this today,
-但是  -是的  我不想
- But? - No, I don't.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
那就不c祝  但你的阿姨寄了c|西
We won't. But your Aunt Jane sent something.
今天到了  所以最好趁地的小偷
It should come today, so it'd probably better to bring it in
拈T廊上偷走前拿M
before the local thieves snatch it from the stoop.
-]人拿的  -真的
- No one's gonna take it. - Really?
告V那居
Tell that to neighbor dude.
他那天放在T廊上的包裹就被偷了
He lost a package the other day right off the front porch.
住在附近的那位老太太也是
Same for the old lady two doors down.
我知道你想干什么
I know what you're trying to do.
你知道
You do, don't you?
你然知道
Of course you do.
S你拿不拿M
Well, bring it in or not, okay?
如果有人在我回家前偷走了  那可不是我的e
It's not my fault if somebody hijacks it before I get home.
再
Bye.
2018年11月9日
V隹职Y援助社^
金伯利
@周有人出^T了
嗯  有纱巫叩搅宋业能道上
好拥  伙
姆  太好了
除我之外有人X得自己要得幽居病了
^Φ  特e是在制家庭rg里
我的感恩要和兄弟姐妹一起^  天
去外面也不行  在里面也不行
我不知道  我X得在里面很安全
因槟愠粤怂
但我感X不
便  生日快  金
不是吧  今天是你生日  生日快钒
死
Shit.
金伯利  @在你T廊上
Kimberly, this was on the front porch.
你能接一下  我要收一下
Can you take it so I can put my umbrella down?
金
Kim?
xx
Thank you.
怎么了
What happened?
我想去拿包裹
I tried to get the package.
好拥
Oh, good for you.
突破自己非常重要
It's important to push your boundaries.
也S我在今天治Y束r能再
Maybe we'll try again at the end of the session.
去道上散散步
You know, take a stroll down the driveway.
看看你的O限
Test your limits.
你今天就17q了  生日快
You turned 17 today. Happy Birthday.
不  只是普通的一天
Yeah. No, just another day.
和往常一
Same as any other.
和往常一邮窃
How are your days the same?
我醒^  Q一度
Well, I wake up. Um, I kind of get dressed.
完成了自W作I
I do my home-school stuff.
坐在房子里  等我爸爸
Sit around the house. Wait for my dad.
然后一起吃晚  看  上床睡X
Then we eat dinner and watch TV, and go to bed.
你X得舍曲林的效果怎么
How are you finding the Sertraline?
我感X很麻木
It makes me feel numb.
麻木是好事是氖
Is numb a good thing or a bad thing?
你爸爸好像是在忙著翻修
I see your dad is still fixing up the place.
是的  他一有空就做
Oh, yeah. When he has the time.
他最近很忙
You know, he's been working a lot lately.
你X得你看到@一F糟怎么f
What do you think your mom would say about all the mess?
是f她能接受翻修的混y
Or was she okay with the home improvement chaos?
你今天想她
Do you, um, want to talk about her today?
你已失去她一年了
It's been almost a year since you lost her.
我知道日和生日
And I know that holidays and birthdays
激起烈的情w
can bring up some really strong emotions.
但我也知道感恩是你和你父H
And I also know Thanksgiving was the last holiday
跟你度^的最后一日
that you and your dad got to spend with your mom.
不  只是普通的一天
No. Just another day,
和往常一
the same as any other.
我收治^很多
I've worked with many people
跟你情r似的病人  金
with similar conditions to yours, Kim.
患有焦]Y和恐慌的病人
People with anxiety disorders, panic attacks.
⒆约汉褪澜绺艚^的病人
The ones who cut themselves off from the world.
但是你的不同在于
But the difference in your case
你在成L  年p的女孩
is you are a developing, young woman,
你得和真人ff
and you need talk to someone real.
你身的人
Someone present.
嗯
Yeah.
我有我爸爸
And I have my dad.
是的  ]e
Yeah. You do.
@真是太傻了
This is so stupid.
e@么吲d
Aw, don't be a party pooper.
好了  _眼睛
Okay, open your eyes.
碓S愿吧
Go on, make a wish.
你S了什么愿
What'd you wish?
如果我告V你  那就不F了  所以
If I tell you, it won't come true, so...
他都是@么f的  l知道"他"都是l
That's what they say, whoever "They" Are.
是P于的
It was about Mom.
可以
Is that okay?
然了
Of course.
戆
Here goes.
看起聿诲e吧
Looks good, huh?
便
Oh, by the way,
我知道你今年不希望
I know you didn't want me to
我大旗鼓地c祝  但是
make a big deal out of things this year, but...
戆  打_吧
Go on. Open it.
嗯
Yeah.
真漂亮
It's so pretty.
戴上
Try it on.
o
Here.
-好  -我想看看
- All right. - I want to see.
很漂亮
It's pretty.
xx你
Thank you.
生日快  H鄣
Happy birthday, sweetheart.
xx你
Thank you.
十一月
你的f圣菜问鞘裁
What's on your Thanksgiving menu?
f圣小N士
我的主N姆・埃金斯有些主意
Tom Elkins, our resident chef, has ideas.
好了  我要上床了
All right, well, I'm headed to bed.
好的  H鄣
All right, sweetheart.
-xx你定的蛋糕  -不用x
- Thanks for the cake. - Of course.
有...@
And...And for this.
你的阿姨o你寄了什么
What'd you get from your aunt?
一些新茶
Just some new teas.
白玫瑰和祁t
White Rose and Keemun,
有一本P于克服恐值
and this book on conquering your fears.
你的阿姨真是[晦
Oh, very subtle, your aunt.
嗯
Yeah.
你出去拿了M
And you got outside to go get it?
很不e
Right? So that's great.
不
No.
桑德斯t生拿M淼
Dr. Saunders had to bring it in.
至少踝×诵≠\  所以...
Well, at least the local thieves were denied, so...
嗯
Yeah.
你今晚吃了
Did you take your meds tonight?
嗯  嗯
Yeah. Yeah.
她想把我送走
Does she want to send me away?
l
Who?
桑德斯t生
Dr. Saunders.
我不知道  有r候我感X
I don't know, sometimes I feel like
她想把我送到t院什么的
she wants to put me away in a hospital or something.
不  H鄣  ]人要把你送走
No, honey, no one's sending you anywhere.
桑德斯t生只是椭你好起
Dr. Saunders is just here to help you through this.
我都是
We both are.
好吧
Okay.
去吧  睡一X
Go on, get some sleep.
-晚安  -晚安  H鄣
- Good night. - Night, sweetheart.
距x感恩有十三天  囤e...
With thirteen days until Turkey Day. Stock up on all...
怎么...
What... ?
金
Kim?!
怎么了  怎么了
What? What?
你能臀疫M行翻修
You think you could start helping me with the renovations?
槭裁
Why?
老f  因槲倚枰椭
Honestly, because I need the help.
就今天臀乙话  行
Please, just help me for the day, yeah?
Come on.
-很有意思  -抱歉
- Very funny. - Oh, sorry.
不  ]P系
Yeah, no, that's okay.
w堑穆╋L太乐亓
There is such a draft coming down from that attic.
也S只是因槟阍ι洗蛄大洞
Maybe it's because you just punched a huge hole in the wall.
是  不  因槲乙往里面bc填料
Yeah? No, it's because I need to put some insulation in.
的待k清
Mom's to-do list.
是在我做完后列出淼  所以
Always after me to get 'er done, so...
F在我做了
high time I did.
我能
Can I?
然了
Oh, yeah, sure.
好的
Cool.
戴上@  跏膏粉m
Put that on. For the plaster dust.
-有@些  -xx
- These, too. - Oh. Thanks.
我能看到屋
I can see all the way up to the top of the house.
-是  -太狂了
- Yeah? - It's crazy.
我在想
I was thinking, um,
感恩  我可以做火u  做c配菜
Thanksgiving I could make a turkey, pick up some sides.
因  可能不
Course, it wouldn't, you know...
不有你做的那么好
Wouldn't be as good as your mom's, but...
我可以  做c特殊的菜
we could try and make something special out of it.
好啊
Sure.
如果你X得你可以搞定
If you think you can handle it.
如果你能臀业脑  那然了
Well, if you give me a hand, you bet.
如果你想要的  我可以...行啊
Yeah. If you want to, I'd... Yeah, I'd like that.
很好  那就在家吃感恩晚餐
All right, good. Thanksgiving dinner at home.
很好
Great.
11月16日
你有什么目
So, do you, um, have any goals?
比如f呢
Like what?
如果你什么都能做
What would you like to do for a living,
你愿意以什么樯呢
if you could do anything?
我不知道
I don't know.
能旅游的工作吧
Something with travel maybe.
旅游
Travel?
很有意思  因...
That's interesting considering...
天天活在@N
Must be a real headache
背景音下肯定很y熬吧
living with this in the background every day.
我T了
I'm used to it.
我爸爸知道自己在做什么
Okay, my dad knows what he's doing.
旅游
Travel?
@不是你常做的事
Isn't that what your mother used to do?
她是一名旅行社代理人
She was a travel agent?
乘T
Flight attendent.
空中服T
Waitress in the sky.
她常是@么自Q的
That's what she used to call it.
我...
I am...
我不是要批u你
I'm not here to judge you,
我也根本不想你失望
and the last thing I want to do is upset you.
但是如果你一直假b]有}
But I can't help if you keep pretending
那我是筒涣四愕
that there are no problems here.
你要我怎么f
What do you want me to say?
你@年o失去母H是一件非常可怕的事
Your mother's death was a terrible loss to endure at your age.
英年早逝是一回事
It's one thing when a person dies before their time,
但年少痛失H人又是另一回事
but it is another thing for them to be taken.
不  你不知道自己在f什么
No, you don't know what you're talking about.
只是因槟悴辉敢夂臀艺f
Only because you won't talk to me.
因槲倦回答你的}了
Because I'm tired of answering your questions!
好  e管我了
Okay? Just leave me alone!
假O我走了
Say I did.
假O我G下你  再也]回
Say I left you alone and didn't come back.
然后呢
Then what?
你X得你好D  是夯
I mean, do you think you'd be better or worse?
@一切的重c就是要信任  金伯利
This whole thing is about trust, Kimberly.
你需要信任我
You need to trust me.
人常因
People beat themselves up
各N可怕的事而怪自己
all the time over the most awful things.
他o法控制的事
Things that they had no control over.
遭遇后  怪自己也是很常的事
And it's common after a traumatic experience to blame yourself.
我槭裁匆那么做
Why would I do that?
又不是我⑺懒怂
I didn't kill her.
你然]有
Of course you didn't.
但你需要承Jl生的事
But you need to acknowledge what happened.
我可以承J
I can acknowledge it.
好吧  一混蛋⑺懒宋
Okay, some sick bastard murdered my mother
把她的尸w扔在了一片空地上
and dumped her body in a vacant lot.
好了  我f出砹
There, I said it.
我F在治愈了
Am I cured now?
我X得你很害怕
I think you're afraid
是因榉赶逻@些罪行的人]有被抓住
because the man who did this was never caught.
也S@就是槭裁茨悴幌腚x_
And maybe that's why you don't want to leave.
Q做是你呢
Well, would you?
我在@里很安全
I'm safe here.
我和我爸爸一起就很安全
I'm safe alone with my dad.
f一他出什么事呢
And what if something happens to him?
你不能永h待在@里
You can't stay in here forever.
外面有大千世界
The world is out there.
你躲在@里  ⑺滥的人就A了
You hide in here, and you let whoever took your mom away win.
A
Win?
天啊  你f得好像一切都是一鲇
God, you make it sound like a game.
我到了你的治
Couldn't help overhearing the session.
夥沼悬co啊
Got a little heated, huh?
抗的治形式
Well, confrontational forms of therapy
能蜃病人振作起
tend to get patients worked up.
我T了
I'm used to it.
她和她有一拥幕盍
She's got the same fire her mom had.
金伯利的治效果不大好  D姆斯先生
Kimberly's, uh, not making very good progress, Mr. Tooms.
她只是需要再多和你待一段rg
She just needs to spend more time with you.
金伯利有]有δ惚憩F出肢w上的_撞
Has Kimberly ever displayed physical aggression toward you?
或者害她自己
Or herself?
不  她不@么做的
No. She wouldn't do that.
她有]有_你妻子l^火
Was she ever angry with your wife?
和_斯  ]有
With Rose? No!
]有  不^是普通的母女吵
Never. I mean, no more than the usual mother/daughter spat.
怎么了
Why?
我只是想更加了解
Well, I'm just trying to get a better picture of Kimberly
金伯利焦]l作的具w情r
and her mental state leading to the onset of the anxiety.
不  她不可能  不可能害任何人
No, she couldn't... couldn't hurt anybody.
特e是她母H  至少^Σ故意
Especially not her mother. Not on purpose.
亨利  你身橐幻家庭成T
You know, Henry, it's easy to miss things
你很容易忽略掉一些事
when you're emotionally enrolled with a family member.
-@是老生常了  -好的  t生
- It's cliche. - Yeah, okay, Doc.
-但是父母是最后一知道的  -嗯
- But parents are often the last to know. - Yeah.
所以一定要注意她的O端行
So, keep an eye out for extreme behaviors.
可能是需要加大用的E象
Now, it could be a sign of the medication,
也可能是病情加重的表F
but it could be a sign of a deeper pathology.
O端行
Extreme behaviors?
金伯利很怒
Well, Kimberly's angry,
怒能表F在多方面
and anger can manifest itself in many ways.
比如f呢
Like what?
妄想  迫  偏
Delusional, obsessive, paranoid.
M可能一人待著
Look, spending as much time as she does alone,
拒^承J自己身上l生的事
refusing to acknowledge what happened to her...
不  著  金伯利v了很多事
No. Look, um, Kimberly's been through a lot.
她熬^淼  的
She'll pull through this. She will.
你很悲
You're grieving,
我知道@δz碚f都不容易
And I know it's not easy. For either of you,
但如果金伯利o法面Πl生的事
but if Kimberly doesn't confront what happened,
@g房子只囊圣所成一Oz
this house will turn from a sanctuary into a cell.
@是她的家
This is her home.
不是一Oz
It's not a prison.
亨利  拜托
Henry, please.
你@犹由著她了  你她出
You're coddling her when you should be coaxing her out,
打破⑺P在里面的怪圈
breaking the cycle that's keeping her inside.
我知道怎么B我的女
I know how to raise my own daughter.
下周
I'll see you next week.
拜托  想想我f的建h
Please, just, um, think about what I said.
抱歉
Sorry.
槭裁
For what?
表F@么差
For being a bitch.
H鄣  你v了  好
Oh honey. You're doing the best you can, all right?
-嗯  -你]事吧
- Yeah. - You okay?
嗯
Well, yeah.
我要去W利酒吧  和他喝妆
I'm gonna head down to O'Malley's, get a beer with the guys.
好的
Okay.
等我回  我能一起看影挖冰淇淋
When I get back, we can watch a movie, pig out on ice cream.
-太好了  -好  乖乖的
- Great. - All right. Be good.
-嗯  你也是  -好
- Yeah. You, too. - All right.
碜约永福尼恩西Z的失少年
A teenager from Encino, California,
在^一周搜索后仍然不影
is still missing after a one-week search
也并]有找的新的索或者目糇C人
has failed to turn up any new leads or witnesses.
警方岩伤鞣啤ぬ├帐窃诙魑髦Z自己家附近被T拐
Police suspect Sophie Taylor was abducted near her Encino home.
在今早ek的l布上
At a press conference earlier this morning,
她的父母┣蠊提供
her parents made an appeal for information
P于他失女旱男畔
concerning their daughter's disappearance.
我只希望大家知道
I just want everyone to know
我女菏美  善良  秀的人
what a beautiful, kind, and wonderful person my daughter is.
如果你在看  索菲
If you're watching this, Sophie,
索菲・泰勒的父母
我非常勰
we love you very much.
我只想知道你]事
We just want to know that you're okay
希望你能回家
and for you to come home.
希望任何知道有P
We're appealing to anyone who knows any information
恩西Z警方峋
索菲・泰勒去向的人
regarding Sophie Taylor's whereabouts
失少女  索菲・泰勒
R上系@a
to contact this number immediately.
天啊
Oh, my God.
刃侣  y^m因樗
In national news, the President is once again under fire
持m攻...
for his continual attack
失少女  索菲・泰勒
失
索菲・泰勒
⒖奸x
失n案
我是失人士  我需要你的椭
下一位
仍然失
消失
今年加州失13086人
好吧
Okay.
死
Shit.
你醒著  我以槟悻F在已睡了
Oh, you're still up. I thought you'd be in bed by now.
我今晚不是要看影
Oh, I thought we had movie night.
是的  我]想到@么晚才能回
Yeah, it just took a little longer than I planned.
臀乙话
Lend a hand?
然了
Oh, sure.
外面很冷
Is it cold outside?
不冷  里有c
Cold? No, well, it's a little chilly in the van.
你都在干什么呢
What have you been up to?
看看
Just watching TV.
有好看的
Anything good?
不  ]什么好看的
No, nothing really.
主要是_浪目
Surfing mostly.
你在唬我  比格_先生
You're bluffing, Mr. Bigelow.
我不知道你想干什么  但是你想_我
I don't know what you're after, but you're trying to trick me.
菲利普太太  你能告V我
Mrs. Phillips, can you tell me...
你不I
You're not hungry?
就是]胃口了
Uh, just lost my appetite, I guess.
冰淇淋的胃口
For ice cream?
我泶
Well, I'll clean up.
-死  -慢c  小冒失鬼
- Shit! - Easy there, jumpy.
抱歉
Sorry.
不  ]P系
No, it's all right.
-不  我能清理干  -我
- No, I can clean it up. - Let me get it.
-小心c  -死
- Careful. - Ow, shit.
死  我要你小心c的
Damn, I told you to be careful.
我看看
Come on, let me see.
-我看看  -]事
- Let me see. - It's fine.
]事的
It's fine.
我看看
Let me see.
不  口不深  但我得好好洗干
No, it's not too deep, but, yeah, we should definitely wash up.
Come on.
好了
Yeah. Okay.
Here you go.
我把血弄到你身上了
I got blood on you.
我不介意
I don't mind.
好了
There we go.
我至少能@湍
Yeah, that's the least I can do.
xx
Thanks.
感恩
爸爸
Hey, Dad?
感恩快  H鄣
Hey, happy Thanksgiving, sweetheart.
嗯
Yeah.
我今天得出去一下
I have to go out for a bit today.
我o你留下做火u的菜
I left instructions for the turkey.
你就花一整天砗煤每
I think you just kind of bake it all day,
隔一段rg硗奎c料
baste every once in a while.
你能做到
Can you handle that for us?
好的
Uh, yeah, sure, um...
我的生日Y物是哪里I的
Hey, where did you get my birthday present?
小巷里的一家首店  怎么了
At a jewelry shop in the Valley. Why?
你_定@不是二手的
Are you sure it's not second-hand?
什么
What?
@都暗了  看到了
Well, it's tarnished. See?
-暗了  -
- Tarnished? - Yeah.
我I的r候]注意到
Didn't see that when I bought it,
但估只是一c小瑕疵
but, um, it's a manufacturing flaw, I suppose.
常有的事
It happens.
那你能不能去Q新的
So then maybe you can exchange it for a new one?
他只有@一了  抱歉  金
It's the only one they had in stock. Sorry, Kim.
把早餐吃了
Here, eat your breakfast.
e放隽
Before it gets cold.
xx
Thanks.
^五年科W
金伯利・D姆斯
真盒
Disgusting.
死
Oh, shit.
_斯・D姆斯
那是...血
Is that... blood?
天啊
Oh, my God.
阿姨  我是金伯利
Hey, Aunty Jane? It's Kimberly.
我知道今天是f圣
I know it's the holidays,
但我真的需要去你那里住滋
but I really, really have to stay with you for a few days.
等我到你后向你解的
Um, I'll explain more when I see you.
回  好的  再
Just give me a call back. Okay, bye.
好的  加油  金伯利
Okay, come on, Kimberly.
加油  加油  加油
Come on, come on, come on.
你不能待在@里  金
You can't stay here, Kim.
好吧
Okay.
只不^是太
It's just the sun.
那只是一些B
That's just some birds.
你]事的
You're gonna be okay.
Gonna be okay.
你]事的
You're gonna be okay.
我回砹
I'm home!
我X得我I到了最后一K南瓜派
Think I found the last pumpkin pie.
今天火u做得怎么
How'd it go with the turkey today?
你B桌子都...
You didn't even set the ta--
@是什么  爸爸
What is this, Dad?
你不用心@些
They're nothing for you to worry about.
@些是你偷的
Did you steal them?
你去w歉墒裁
What were you even doing in the attic?
我只是想去看看你都在干什么
I just wanted to see what you've been doing.
看什么  我一直在b修房子
See what? I've been working on the house.
老f  金  我X得你停止
Honestly, Kim, I think you have to stop
@些o端的猜y
with these wild assumptions.
我可以到你在上面走碜呷
I can hear you moving around up there.
大半夜
At night.
你就在干@N事
Is this what you've been doing?
藏著些|西
Hiding these?
爸爸
Dad!
我可以有我的[私  金
I'm allowed to have my own private things, Kim.
但你槭裁匆@影阉藏起
But why would you hide them like that?
-死  金  @干的  -爸爸
- Damn it, Kim! It's gonna be dry! - Dad?
所以我和你不o你I
See, this is why your mother and I never got you a cat.
你槭裁窗堰@些藏在以前工作用旅行箱里
Why would you hide them in Mom's old work bag?
我很想你的  金
I miss your mom, Kim.
和你一  我想要[藏
Same as you. I try to hide it,
但有r候我只是需要和
but sometimes I just need to spend some time alone
她的z物为待一
with the few remaining pieces that she left behind.
儆谖业|西  只儆谖
Pieces that are mine. Just mine.
金
Kim?
H鄣  我很抱歉@你很y^
Look sweetheart, I'm sorry if it upset you,
但爸爸不完美
but Dad's not perfect.
@上面有血
There's blood on this.
那是涂料
That's paint.
阿姨
你不接
You're not gonna answer that?
不  F在不接
No, not right now.
你吃了
Are you taking your meds?
什么
What?
桑德斯t生f可能有一些副作用
Well, Dr. Saunders said there might be side effects--
激M的行  妄想
erratic behavior, paranoia.
不是因樗  e把矛^饰
It's not the med-- Don't turn this around on me!
金  f  你F在又有妄想的表F了
Kim, I gotta be honest with you. You're acting paranoid again.
-明明什么事都]有  -e再撒e了
- Over nothing. Really nothing! - Just stop lying!
eξ掖蠛粜〗  我是你爸爸
Don't take that tone with me! I am still your father!
你⒘怂
Did you kill her?
什么  l
What?! Who?
索菲・泰勒
Sophie Taylor.
@是她的
This is her necklace, isn't it?
不是
Well, isn't it?!
拜托  爸爸  真相
Come on, Dad, the truth.
不f  好吧
Not gonna tell the truth? Fine.
@是一拥
They're the same.
一拥
Same mark.
我^店里了
Yeah, I talked to the store.
但他f@是流行
Yeah, but they said it's a style.
他f@叫"痛苦"
Distressed, they called it.
好吧
Okay.
那@些呢
Well, what about these?
@些都是l的
Who did they belong to?
@些都是你的
They belonged to your mother.
她@些年在wC上找到的首
Pieces she picked up from flights over the years.
她上交的
She should've turned them in
o失物招I什么的  但是
to lost and found or whatever, of course, but...
你并不完美
you know, your mom was not perfect.
我并不完美
I'm not perfect.
你并不完美
You're not perfect.
我不想告V你  f一你...
I didn't want to tell you in case you...
抓狂了呢
freaked out.
但那不能解
But that doesn't explain--
你正在成她  你知道
You're turning into her, do you know that?
最后成妄想Y和神|
Neurotic and paranoid until the end.
你⒘怂
Did you kill her?
不  金
No, Kim.
天啊  你⒘
Oh, my God, did you kill Mom?
⑺滥的人
The person who killed your mother
仍然在逃
is still out there.
或者他一直以
Or he's been here with me
都和我一起
the whole time.
金  拜托
Kim, come on, now!
金  等等
Kim, wait.
-金  -不
- Kim. - No.
- Kim? Ah! - No.
金  _T  拜托  @太蠢了
Kim, open up. Come on now. This is silly.
我]做e什么
I didn't do anything wrong.
金伯利  我勰
Kimberly? I love you.
so_T
Now open up.
不管你在里面做什么
Whatever you're doing in there,
不要到你自己  H鄣
just don't hurt yourself, sweetheart.
金伯利
Kimberly?!
soo我把T打_
I said open this damn door!
把T打_
Open the damn door!
好吧
All right.
我档饺  我就M砹
I'm gonna count to three, and then I'm coming in.
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three!
我缶了
I'm calling the police!
911急救  有什么需要的
911 Emergency. How may I direct your call?
是我爸爸
Um, it's my dad.
我X得他想  他想M入我的房g
I think he's trying-- He's trying to get in my room.
好的  告V我你叫什么名字
Okay, okay. Can I take your name please?
金伯利・D姆斯
Kimberly Tooms.
好的  金伯利  能告V我你住在哪里
All right, Kimberly, can you give me your location?
S多利大道14  回公@
Uh, 14 Victoria Avenue, Echo Park.
你的o急情r是怎么回事
What's the nature of your emergency?
你f你的爸爸想M入你的房g
You said your dad is trying to get into your room?
-我X得他在追⑷  -他在追⒄l
- Yeah, I think he's hurt someone. - Who has he hurt?
我不知道  你能派人兔
I don't know. Can you just send help?
我正在派一警T前往你的地址
I'm dispatching a police unit to your address now.
你的T上有i
Is there a lock on your door?
嗯  我已i上了
Yeah, I already locked it.
很好  待在里面  救援R上
That's good. Stay there. Help is coming.
我X得他回砹
I think he's coming back.
金伯利
Kimberly?
金伯利  e祀
Kimberly, stay on the line.
exT太近  H鄣
Stand back from the door, sweetheart.
稍等一下
Just a second!
-不  R上M砹
- No! - Almost in!
金伯利
Kimberly!
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
你在干什么  so下
What are you doing? Get away from there!
-不  不  -你干什么  下
- No! No! - What are you doing?! Come on! Stop it!
我不害你  我不害你
I'm not gonna hurt you! I'm not gonna hurt you!
蛄
I said that's enough!
好
Okay?
你冷o下砹
Are you calm now?
我你  金  你冷o下砹
I asked you a question, Kim! Are you calm now?!
我能不能好好
Can we please just talk about
安o地@些事  可以
this quietly and sensibly? Can we do that?
我只是最近毫μ大了
It's just that I've been under a lot of stress lately.
H此而已
That's all.
每人都@
This just happens to everybody.
你ol打了
Who did you call?
]l
No one.
最近通
H鄣
Oh, sweetheart.
真希望你]有@么做
I really wish you hadn't done that.
]事  我能解Q的
It's okay. We'll sort this whole mess out.
我F在怎么k
So, what are we gonna do now?
警察在淼穆飞狭
Police are on their way,
你有很多事要向他解
so you're gonna have a lot of explaining to do.
你也是
So do you.
我不在了  l碚疹你呢
So, who's gonna take care of you when I'm not around?
你有]有考]^呢
Did you think of that?
不  ]有我  你就]有容身之
No, without me, there's no roof over your head.
]有容身之所  我必提醒你
A roof, which I'd like to point out,
你甚至都不敢走出去
that you're too afraid to get out from under anyway.
可能只流落到精神病院
Probably just wind up in a damn nut house.
你M橡z房  穿Bw衣
Rubber rooms and straightjackets for you.
你才是需要椭的人
You're the one who needs help.
我什么毒]做
I didn't do anything.
你才是有妄想  出F幻X
You're acting paranoid. Delusional.
不是@拥
That's not true.
好吧  我f
All right, you listen to me.
你_定
Are you sure?
H鄣  你最了解我了
Sweetheart, you've known me your whole life.
我一直都在你身
I've always been there for you.
我]打^你
I never hit you.
我]害^你
I never hurt you.
基本]大f^
Barely even raise my voice.
是
Have I?
Well, have I?
因槲勰  金伯利  你ξ碚f就是一切
Because I love you, Kimberly. You mean everything to me.
那@些首呢
But what about the jewelry?
我不相信那是的
I mean, I just don't believe it was Mom's.
你相信什么并不重要
Doesn't matter what you believe.
我很抱歉被你找到了
I'm sorry you found it.
真的
I really am.
@一直很y^
It hasn't been easy.
你母H的遭遇的_很可怕
What happened to your mother is an awful thing,
但你不能怪我
but you can't blame me for that.
我知道你恨我  真的
I know you hate me, I get it.
我最近的_δ阌悬c疏h
I have been somewhat remote lately.
但我有太多事要操心
But I've had so much on my mind.
我只是希望@第一
I just wanted this first
]有你母H的感恩能...
Thanksgiving without your mother to be...
我也不知道  你能...
I don't know, somehow...
X得可以
okay for you.
我都能
For us.
但我是一名⑷朔
But am I guilty of being a murderer?
你怎么能有@N想法
How can you even think that?
等那些警察砹
So when those police officers show up,
你必要明_@一c
you need to be certain of that.
你@里要明白
You need to know in here,
你@里也要明白
and you need to know in here.
毋庸置疑
Without any doubt.
不然  你就У粑家庭剩余的一切
Otherwise, you'd destroy what's left of our family.
那么F在
So, now
你X得你百分百_J
do you feel that you're one hundred percent positive
我是你J榈哪欠N人
that I am who you think I am?
很好
Good.
那么等警察砹  什么都ef
Then when the police officers do show up, don't say anything.
是物
It's the medication
和你的病情y了你的大X
and your condition that's warping your thinking.
他明白的
They'll understand.
晚上好  先生
Evening, sir.
我是福斯特警官
I'm Officer Foster,
@是班克斯警官  我是洛杉警局的
this is Officer Banks, LAPD.
晚上好
Evening.
我半小r前接到@地址的一缶
We received a 911 call from this address in the last half hour.
一名年p女子Q自己有麻
A young woman said she was in distress.
那是我的女
Yeah, that would be my daughter.
-你是屋主  -是的
- Are you the homeowner? - Yes.
你叫什么名字
And your name?
亨利・D姆斯
Henry Tooms.
D姆斯先生  根那通
Mr. Tooms, on the basis of this call,
我有正理由M入你的住所M行搜查
we have just cause to enter your property to conduct a search
并δ愫湍愕呐哼M行
and to interview both you and your daughter.
你有什么意
Do you have a problem with this?
]有  M
No, please, come in.
抱歉屋里很y
Apologies for the mess.
翻修
Renovations.
你是金伯利  是你缶的
Are you Kimberly? Did you make the 9-1-1 call?
-是的  -其有c擂
- Yeah. - It's a bit embarrassing, actually.
金反^度了
Kim just overreacted.
D姆斯先生  你r
Mr. Tooms, we're gonna need you
x_@房g
to step outside the room for a minute.
槭裁
Why?
我要为和金伯利
I'm gonna need talk to Kimberly alone,
我的搭n去N房
and my partner, she's gonna take
o你做P
your statement in the kitchen there.
好吧
All right.
After you.
我是班克斯警官
I'm Officer Banks.
有什么需要我椭的
Can I get you anything?
不
No.
你受了
Are you injured?
]有
No.
你爸爸最近在翻修
So your dad's renovating, huh?
Oh. Um, yeah.
已忙活了一了
It's been taking a while.
-我能坐  -好的
- May I? - Sure.
-不  不  -抱歉
- Ooh! No, no. - Sorry.
不  不  我戆  @是我的
No, no, I got it. It's mine.
金伯利  我需要你告V我
Kimberly, I'm gonna need you to tell me
今晚l生了什么
what happened here tonight.
你可以告V我
Think you can do that for me?
假日肯定接到很多缶吧
You must get a lot of bogus domestic calls at the holidays.
你槭裁催@么f
What makes you say that?
就是合家F聚  夥崭q
Well, I just mean, families together, tempers flare.
接下
Next thing you know,
淌迨蹇赡芫陀貌孀邮裁吹耐绷吮R侄子
Uncle Joe stabs Cousin Lou with a fork kinda thing.
有可能
It happens.
金伯利  你爸爸F在不在  只有我和你
Kimberly, your dad's not here right now. It's just you and me.
你打肯定是有原因的
You made the call for a reason.
告V我你槭裁匆打
Just tell me what-- what made you pick up the phone.
]什么
Nothing.
他f得  我反^度
He's right. I overreacted.
字幕
So, your daughter's prone to this kind of behavior?
不  她
No, she's...
她是好姑娘  今年λ碚f太y了
She's such a good girl. It's just been a tough year.
她的母H去年被⒘
Her mother was murdered last year.
-_斯・D姆斯  -是的
- Rose Tooms? - Yeah.
哀
Sorry for your loss.
警察]抓到@家伙
Yeah, well, the cops haven't found the guy yet.
你是f她是因檫@才打的
So you're suggesting this is the reason she made that call?
警官  我女哪r起就一直]T不出
Officer, my daughter's been a shut-in since this happened.
她甚至都]法x_@房子
She can't even leave the house.
只要前T一打_  她就恐慌l作
She'll have a panic attack when the front door opens.
我打_窗  她都^
I can't unlatch a window without her getting dizzy.
她一直在吃治...
She's taking this medication for, uh...
V隹植腊Y
Agoraphobia?
]e
Yep.
-你有在M行治  -我爸爸臀艺伊酥委
- Are you seeking treatment for that? - My dad got me a therapist.
我在家里治
We have sessions at home.
你的t生叫什么名字
Can you tell me the name of your doctor?
海・桑德斯t生
Dr. Helen Saunders.
我可以系她
And would it be okay with you if I contacted her?
我最近都]怎么在家
I haven't been around as much.
工作真是忙牧
And work's been, like, crazy.
榱速X供我z生活
Trying to support the both of us.
她只是太孤魏怒
Uh, she's just lonely and angry.
我之前f了她拙  她就跑到巧先チ
I told her off earlier, she ran upstairs.
青少年
Teenagers.
你槭裁匆f她
Why'd you tell her off?
@房子...
Well, the house is just--
最近在是太y了
it's all over the place right now, you know?
好吧
All right.
她上了w  我告V她  我也不知道
She went up to the attic, and I told her-- Well, I don't know.
她上去看到了一些她以前的|西
She was up there to see some of her mom's old stuff,
于是  你懂的
so, like, you know.
但她都快摔嗖弊恿  所以我
But she practically broke her neck, so I got--
我  我失控了
I just-- I lost it,
她就跑回了房g  不愿意出
so she ran to her room, wouldn't come out.
我的音就有c大
You know, I raised my voice with her a bit.
我X得她一r接受不了
I don't think she was used to it.
她就o你打了
She called you guys.
D姆斯先生  家庭暴力是非常乐
Mr. Tooms, domestic abuse is a serious issue.
我常接到@N缶
We get a lot of calls on it.
所以我必要你
So I have to ask...
你以前打^她
have you ever hit her before?
不  ]有
No. Never.
他]有δ舆^手
He's never raised his hand to you in any way?
不  我就是太生饬
No. I was just mad.
@...我不那诱f的
This is-- I shouldn't have said anything.
我不...
I don't--
我不想o他惹上麻
I don't want him to get in any trouble.
我明白  他是你爸爸
I understand that. He's your dad.
他  他]做e什么
He-- He hasn't done anything wrong.
你_定你]有e的事想告V我了
Are you sure there's nothing else you want to tell me?
我_定
Yeah, I'm sure.
那  我X得我完了
Okay then, I think we're done here.
看起硎堑
Yeah, it appears so.
你爸爸所Q
According to your dad,
@一切都只是一`
this was all some sort of misunderstanding.
-  -Σ黄
- Is that correct? - I'm sorry.
既然如此
In that case,
我需要警告你下次不得再浪M警方的事件
I'm gonna have to caution you against wasting police time.
只有在真正出事r才能打o我
We're only to be called in cases of genuine emergencies.
明白了
Do you understand?
嗯  我很抱歉
Yes, I'm sorry.
好了  如果]有e的事了
All right, if there's nothing else...
好的  那我走了
Okay, then we'll head out.
勰
Love you.
是xx你的到
Thanks for coming just the same.
-祝你晚安  -xx
- You have a good night. -Thank you.
稍等一下
Hey, hold on one second.
著  如果你有什么你X得
Hey, listen, if there's anything that you want to talk about
你不能在@里f的事
that you feel like you can't talk about here,
直接打o我
call me direct, okay?
-好的  -什么事都行
- Okay. - Anything at all.
xx
Thanks.
晚安  再次xx你
Night. Thanks again.
日快
Happy holidays.
上床  我明早修你的T
Go to bed. I'll fix your door in the morning.
t生咨W
搜索你的物
丙酚
o}滴注用于麻醉
副作用  缺失
有人
我需要椭
姆
沙
你M^我房g
You were in my room.
我如果翻你的私人物品  你怎么想
How would you feel if I went through your personal things?
我感到失望
Should I be disappointed?
生
Angry?
是馕易约]把你教育好
Or mad at myself for not bringing you up right?
我到了
I hurt myself.
o我
Give me that.
槭裁
Why?
因檫@是我的
Because it's mine.
@不在你的收藏里
This wasn't in your collection.
-o我  -你知道最奇怪的是什么
- Just give it to me. - You know what's weird?
什么
What?
不的那些女孩
All those girls that went missing?
她看起矶己芟
They all kinda look the same.
她都有c像
They kinda look like Mom.
@一切都_始失控了
This whole thing's getting out of hand.
我勰  我勰  金
I love you, and I loved your mom, Kim.
我的家庭ξ碚f是最重要的事
Our family, it was and is the most important thing to me.
你失那晚  我吵了架
The night your mom disappeared, we fought.
_斯又一次在最后P^改了
Rose had a last-minute schedule change. Again.
我受蛄
And I was tired of it.
我受虿槐凰放在第一位
I was tired of not being first.
我和你不被放在第一位
Of you and me not being first.
我后悔我吵架r我f的
Do I regret every word of that fight?
然了  每天每一分每一秒
Yes! Every minute, every second of every day.
但是警察找到了你的尸w
But when the cops found your mom's body,
拜托  相信我  我的心永h碎了
please, you gotta believe me, my heart broke forever.
我也希望能收回那些  收回那些怒
I wish I could take those words and take the anger out of them
用岢篮湍托砣〈
and replace it with compassion and patience.
我F在就在@么做
Which is what I'm doing now.
你X得我想失去你
Do you think I wanna lose you?
你X得我桑德斯t生你住院
Do you think I'm gonna let Dr. Saunders have you committed?
金伯利  不
Kimberly, no!
我只有我了
All I have is us!
金  拜托  o我吧
Kim, please, please just give it to me,
去睡X吧  明天一切都好的
go to sleep, and everything will be better in the morning.
金伯利
Kimberly.
金
Kim.
-收起  -多少人
- Put that away! - How many?
你到你自己的
You're gonna hurt yourself.
多少人
How many?
桑德斯t生之前就提醒^我
This is exactly what Dr. Saunders warned me about.
她f你的物可能你有攻粜
She said your medication might trigger aggression.
她要我小心  我]有
She told me to look for this, and I didn't listen.
如果你到了自己  到我  你就被P起
If you hurt yourself, if you hurt me, you'll be locked up.
不要
Stay where you are, please.
那天晚上不HH只有我和她吵了架
I wasn't the only one who fought with her that night!
你不得了
You don't remember that, do you?
你不得你那晚有多么怒
You don't remember how angry you were at her that night.
-不是@拥  -不是
- That's not true. - It's not?
-不是@拥  -你_定
- That's not true. - Are you sure?
-你走吧  -金  不是你想的@
- Go! Leave! - Kim, it's not what you think!
-信我@一次  -信你
- Just trust me for once! - Trust you?
我槭裁匆信背叛我爸爸的人
Why would I trust someone who's cheating on my dad?
-我]有  -你x_了他  x_了我
- I'm not! - You leave him. You leave me.
你x_了我  走吧
You leave us! Leave!
-e再回砹  -金
- And don't bother coming back here! - Kim!
金伯利  把刀o我
Kimberly, just give me the knife
趁一切]到不可挽回的地步
before something happens you can't take back.
金伯利
Kimberly.
-放下  -我fe靠近我
- Put that down. - I said stay away from me.
后退
Stay back!
不
No.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
住手  不不不
Stop. No, no, no!
感恩快
Happy Thanksgiving.
黑色星期五
爸爸
Dad?
爸爸  你在
Dad?! Are you there?!
有人
Hello?!
爸爸
Dad.
爸爸  M
Dad? Please come in.
e@么ξ
Don't do this to me!
我更多的是失望  而不是怒
It's more disappointment than anger.
你我eox  金
You leave me no choice here, Kim.
你失控了
You're out of control.
@不是永久的
This isn't permanent.
@不是土P
It's not punishment.
我o你留了晚
I even left you some of the dinner,
我本硪一次吃的日晚餐
the holiday dinner we were supposed to have,
包括派
including the pie,
老f  不o你吃的
which, frankly, you don't deserve.
你能好好想清楚
That should tide you over for now.
在你安定下碇前  不得使用你的手C或X
Your phone and your laptop are off-limits until you settle down.
H鄣  我要出去一下
Honey, I need to go out for a little bit,
所以我等我回砗笤僬f@件事
so we'll finish talking about this when I get back.
爸爸
Dad?
Dad?!
你不能@么做
Hey! You can't do this!
You can't do this!
好吧
Okay. Okay.
操
Fuck. Fuck!
Fuck.
太好了
Yes.
金伯利
Kimberly.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
你得我在你小r候你去看的魔g表演
Remember when I took you to that magic show when you were a kid?
他把一女人]了
They made a woman disappear.
得  他把她i在盒子里
Yeah. Remember, they locked her in a box, and poof!
她就不了
She was gone.
你靠向我
You leaned over to me,
道  "爸爸  他怎么做到的"
you said, "Daddy, how'd they do that?"
得我怎么f的  得
Remember what I said? Remember?
"@是魔法
"It's magic.
那女人r消失
The woman will disappear for a bit,
但是她永h出"
but she will always come out."
我那一周都在屋子里玩捉迷藏
We spent the whole week playing hide-and-seek all over the house.
你知道
And you know what?
我是能找到你
I always found you.
你是出
And you always came out.
出戆
Please, come out.
那好吧
Right, then.
金伯利
Kimberly!
捂上耳朵  H鄣
Watch your ears, sweetheart.
拜托
Come on!
稍等一下  我R上砹
Just a little more, I'll be right there!
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
我是亨利
Jane? It's Henry.
我]事  你好
Oh, I'm fine. Yeah, how are you?
不  其  她F在
Uh, no, actually, right this second,
正在忙
she's in the middle of something.
我能等她忙完后她打o你
So, uh, hey, I could get her to call you back when she's finished.
-她o你打了  什么r候  -救命
- She called you? When? - Help!
-她有c患了幽居病  -救命
- She is feeling a little cabin fever. - Help me!
-@是好事    -救命
- So, that's a good sign, right? - Help me, please!
-救命  -我想她可能
- Help! - I just think maybe
-她非常想要  -救命
- She was a little overzealous... - Help me!
出去^夜
...about asking for a sleepover.
然了  的
Absolutely, you should, yeah.
金伯利很想你
Kimberly would love to see you, you know.
@影  o我滋
Tell you what, give me a couple of days.
f在的  房子里F在一F糟
Honestly, the place is a mess.
我把房子整理一下
If I can just get the house in order.
保重
Mm-hmm. Yeah, take care.
我的上帝啊
Jesus fucking Christ.
那是你的阿姨
So that was your Aunt Jane.
她f你o了留言f要去她那菏裁吹
She said you had left a message. Something about making a trip?
你@又我越碓皆  H鄣
You're not doing us any favors, honey.
金
Kim?
拜托  我得下戆涯阕コ鋈
Oh, come on, do I have to come down in there and get you?
死
Damn it!
金伯利
Kimberly?
我知道你很害怕  金  但我X得你不明白
I know you're scared, Kim, but I don't think you get it.
我是想湍  我是你父H
I'm trying to help you. I'm your father.
我勰
I love you.
不管你做了什么
Doesn't matter what you did.
你要保持^Π察o  乖乖我f的做
You're gonna remain completely quiet and do exactly as I say.
不然  有人就受
Otherwise, someone is gonna get hurt.
金伯利
Kimberly.
上去
Go.
桑德斯t生
Dr. Saunders?
抱歉我有ct到了
Hi. I'm sorry I'm running a bit late.
今天真是像噩粢
It's been a nightmare of a day.
后的混y和黑五的狂g
There's all this post-holiday chaos and Black Friday mania.
我打告V你我要t到了
I should have called and said I was running behind.
你]事吧
Are you okay?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你看上去...很K
Well, you look... dirty.
是的  我一直在b修房子
Oh. Yeah, I've been working on the house.
我能M
May I come in?
我得Qrg了
We're gonna have to reschedule, actually.
我有很多活要干
Yeah, I got a lot of work to do,
F在不是r候
and it's not a good time right now.
爸爸
Dad?
]事
It's okay.
她可以M
She can come in.
我X得F在@不是一好主意
I don't think it's a good idea right now.
桑德斯t生大老h的^
Dr. Saunders came all this way.
]事的
It's fine.
我可以待涸俑愣  Π
We could finish up later, right?
好吧
Okay.
-你真]_玩笑  -]e
- Oh, wow, you weren't kidding. - Yeah.
@里好像爆炸^
Looks like a bomb went off in here.
是啊  今天真是忙牧
Yeah, it's kind of a rough day.
今天去那里吧
Um, better in here today.
好吧
Okay.
你爸爸o你事情做也挺好的吧
Well, it's a good thing your dad's keeping you busy, though.
嗯
Yeah.
著  今天我就在@旁吧
Uh, listen, I'm gonna sit in on this one.
如果你不介意的
If that's okay with you.
好吧
Okay.
你在服用你的
So, um, are you still taking your medication?
不
No.
槭裁
Why not?
我想我忘了
I guess I forgot.
那你不吃感X怎么
Then how are you feeling without it?
我的X袋更清楚了
My head's clearer.
恐慌l作更加l繁是有所p少
And have the panic attacks, have they increased or decreased?
我不知道  有r我感X自己被困住了
I don't know, sometimes I feel trapped.
被困住了
Trapped?
困在@房子里
In this house.
不是字面上的意思
Not literally.
槭裁
How so?
就像我想要出去
Like I want to get out,
但我做不到
but I can't.
好吧  是什么r住了你
Okay. What's holding you back?
我不知道我爸爸怎么
I don't know what will happen to my dad.
你心如果你x_  可能就再也不到你爸爸
So you're afraid if you leave, you might not see your dad again?
更像是我再也不回砹
More like I won't come back.
@就叫L大  金
Well, that's called growing up, Kim.
我最后都v@一步
And it happens to all of us eventually.
孩子x_
Children leave.
但是一步一步
But one step at a time.
我先你走出前T吧  好
Let's just get you out the front door first, okay?
我]o你什么喝的
I never offered you a drink.
不用  我]事  xx
Oh, no, I'm fine. Thank you.
不不不  我泡的茶很好
No, no, no, I make a great cup of tea.
我的阿姨  她是我的妹妹
And my Aunt Jane, she's my mom's sister,
o我寄了一些新茶~
just sent me these new teas to try,
我想全部混在一起  做我的特制茶
and I like to mix them together and make my own.
我有伯爵夫人茶   黑加霾
I've got Lady Grey, Black Currant.
有c像伯爵t茶  你知道
Kinda like Black Grey, you know?
-金  她不要  -你_定
- Kim, she's fine. - Are you sure?
e逼她了
Stop pushing.
好吧  我要
You know what? Um, yes.
我要  我想著名的金伯利・D姆斯茶
Yes, I would like to try the famous Kimberly Tooms brew.
太好了
Great.
我F在就去做
I will go make that now.
除非你想去做
Unless you'd like to make it.
不
No.
桑德斯t生想要金特制茶
Dr. Saunders would like a Kim special.
你想要的我可以o你也泡一杯
I can make you one too if you want.
好  e花太久就行
Sure. Just don't take too long.
需要椭
缶
-一切都好吧  -很好
- Everything okay in there? - Fine.
感恩^得怎么
How was Thanksgiving?
好了
Okay, there we go.
xx
Thank you.
@杯是什么
Which one is this?
我x了祁Tt茶
Uh, I chose the Keemun,
加了c白玫瑰
with a pinch of the White Rose.
可能不好喝
It could suck.
@是t茶  所以只有牛奶和糖
It's black tea, so just, you know, milk and sugar.
我X得牛奶牧
Think the milk turned.
我X得很好喝  我明白槭裁匆大M周章了
I think it's lovely. I see what all the fuss is about.
我想我
I want to talk about my mom.
好  然可以了  如果你想的
All right. Um, we can certainly do that, if you feel up to it.
我想
I do.
也S我可以慢慢
Maybe we could take our time with that.
如果金伯利想要  那@是她的x
Uh, if Kimberly wants to talk about that, it's her choice.
她在治^程中想f什么都行
She can go wherever she wants to in these sessions.
我想
I do want to talk about it.
f吧
Go ahead.
我最近想了很多
I've been thinking about it a lot lately.
P于她的遭遇  有那
You know, about what happened to her, and the man--
那⑺浪的人
the man who killed her.
我想^很多如果我有C的
I thought a lot about what I would say to him
我λf什么
if I ever had the chance.
你要f什么呢
And what would that be?
我不他槭裁
I wouldn't ask him why.
不
No.
我知道槭裁
I know why.
他@么做因樗是B
He did it because he's sick.
因樗很享受
Because he enjoys it.
他也So自己找理由
He probably justifies it to himself.
那N人樽约旱乃作所檎胰魏谓杩
A man like that invents excuses to do what he does.
解他的病B
To excuse his own sickness.
你得你第一次告V我我是在一O里
Remember you first told me that I was in a cocoon?
就像一只暝的蝴蝶
Like a butterfly struggling to get out?
也S他也在O里
Maybe he's in a cocoon, too.
只不^  他躲在他的O里
Except... he hides in his,
那里黑暗
where it's dark...
]人能看到
where no one can see him
真正的他
for what he really is.
我告V他  他是禽F  懦夫
And I'd tell him he's a monster and a coward.
你X得他δ阏f什么
And what do you think he would say to you?
恐怕今天就到此橹沽
I'm afraid that's all the time we have for today.
房子里有很多活要干
So much work to do around the house.
抱歉  t生
Sorry, Doctor.
嗯
Right. Well, um,
我X得我今天有新的突破  金伯利
I think we were breaking new ground here, Kimberly.
也S下一次治  我可以出T
Um, maybe at our next session, we can venture outside
也S能去院子里
maybe into the yard?
我很愿意
I'd like that.
你的茶很棒
Great job with the tea.
五星好u
Five stars.
xx你  t生
Well, thank you, Doctor.
其我要你z一些事
Um... I actually need to ask you both something.
-什么事  -我昨晚接到
- What's that? - I got a call last night
是一名叫班克斯的警官
from an Officer Banks, I believe?
她f@地址有人缶
She said they were called to this address.
她想_J我是不是金伯利的t生
She wanted to confirm that I was Kimberly's doctor.
有什么事要告V我
Is there anything I should know?
-]有  -]有
- No. - No.
]有
No.
好吧
All right.
-周末愉快  -xx
- Oh, um, have a good weekend. - Thank you.
需要椭
缶
好
Okay.
你麻┐罅
You are in so much trouble!
你那么想知道
You wanted to know.
F在你知道了
Now you know.
我要理掉她  金
I'm gonna have to get rid of her, Kim.
我不喜g@痈苫
I don't like to work like this.
我喜g小心  精_  不留痕E
I like to be careful, precise, no traces.
@些女孩需要被土P
These girls need to be punished.
我不能她影到你
I can't let them influence you.
我不能你暴露在她的影下
I can't risk you being exposed to what they are.
我是在保o你  金
I protect you, Kim.
你知道的
You know that, right?
@就是我在@世上的目的  榱吮Ｗo你的安全
That's my purpose on earth, to make it safer for you.
等你哪愕睦O里出
For when you come out of your cocoon.
挠贾谐r
Upon emerging from its chrysalis,
蝴蝶于其生命周期中最脆弱的A段
the butterfly is at its most vulnerable state in its life cycle.
在那之前  它w不了
Until that's done, it can't fly.
它只成轼B和其他捕食者的C物
And then it's easy prey for birds and other predators.
你的聿焕斫
Your mother never understood that.
不^  她也]椭^我
But then again, she never helped us
完成你的五年科W目  是
with your fifth-grade science fair project, either, did she?
第二名  多么自豪
Second place. So proud.
但是她lF...
But then when she found out...
@直就像把破碎的玻璃杯拼回起
yeah, it was like trying to put broken glass back together.
我能怎么k
What was I supposed to do?
她只告V警察
She was just gonna tell the cops,
然后他就永h地ё吣
and then they'd take you away from me forever.
我只是勰愣已
I never did anything but love you.
我已M可能做到更好了
I did the best I could under the circumstances.
你不想f些什么什么
Do you not have anything to add?
你不想c任
You don't want to take a little personal responsibility for this?
是你干的  @都是你的e  金伯利
You did this. This is your fault, Kimberly.
如果你能乖乖
Dr. Saunders would still be alive
桑德斯t生F在能活著
if you just did as you were told.
但你就是做不到  你]法遵守
But you couldn't do it. You couldn't toe the line.
F在成@
And now this is where we are.
如果你是像孩子一  你只被孩子
If you act like a child, you'll be treated like one.
我不是娜  根本不是
I'm not a bad man. Not at all.
有一天  你走出那扇T
One day, you're gonna walk out that door,
你明白  我槟阕@世界更加安全
and you'll get that I made the world a safer place for you.
@些女孩
These girls...
@些女人  都想要你...
these women, they all want you to...
要你和她一
Well, just want you to be like them.
就算你]^她
Even if you haven't met them,
她的影  她的能量  都在外面
their influence, their energy, it's out there.
我^Σ允S
And I would never allow that.
永h
Ever.
你是我的小女
You're my girl.
我碛羞^最好的|西
The best thing I ever did.
我永h槟
I always did everything for...
做一切
for you.
槲
F-For us.
操你的
Fuck you.
你
Hey... you just...
金
Kim...
丙酚
Propofol.
太好了
Oh, yes. Okay.
操  拜托
Fuck, come on.
好了
Okay.
快接  快接
Pick up, pick up.
了
Cell phone ringing.
是提姆・W利
Is that Tim O'Day calling?
天  f一真的是呢
Oh, my God, what if it is?
我是班克斯  你好
Banks. Hello?
你好  我是金伯利・D姆斯
Yeah. Hi, it's Kimberly Tooms.
你得  你f要是
Remember, you said to call--
要是l生了什么事  就o你打
to call you if something bad happened?
我得
Yeah, I remember.
是我爸爸  你得so^
It's my Dad. You have to come now, okay?
你得把他抓起
You have to take him away.
-他害你了  -他⒘怂
- Has he hurt you? - He killed her.
索菲・泰勒  上失的那女孩
Sophie Taylor? You know, the missing girl from the TV?
我X得他⒘似渌人
I think he's killed other girls.
他在我面前⑺懒宋业闹委
I mean, he killed my therapist right in front of me.
我]e吧
Am I hearing you right?
你f你爸爸在你面前⒘巳
You're telling me your dad killed somebody in front of you?
-是的  -你爸爸F在在哪里  金伯利
- Yes. - Okay, where's your dad now, Kimberly?
他  他在地板上倒了
Um, he's... he's passed out on the floor.
我o他下了
I drugged him.
但是我不知道能持m多久
But I don't know how much longer it's going to last.
我需要你F在R上x_那幢房子
Okay, I just need you to get out of the house immediately, okay?
我不知道我行不行
I don't know if I can, okay?
他把所有|西都藏了起  我被i在@里了
He boarded everything up. I'm locked in.
不要  好
Stay on the line, okay?
-怎么回事  -那晚的缶
- What is it? - That domestic from the other night.
金伯利・D姆斯
Kimberly Tooms?
她f是她父H⑺懒怂鞣啤ぬ├
She said her father's the one that killed Sophie Taylor.
操
Fuck!
-金  你在  -嗯
- Kim, you still with me? -Yes.
金伯利  我需要你sox_房子
Kimberly, I need you to get out of the house
跑的越h越好  行
and get as far away as you possibly can, okay?
我的警察在路上了  你到了
We've go units on the way, okay? Can you hear me?
我昨晚撒e了
Yeah, look, I lied yesterday.
的_有事
Something's wrong.
死
Oh, shit.
金
Kim?
他
He's--
金伯利
Kimberly--
你下的不足以麻倒我@w型
You didn't use enough for someone my size.
但是白玫瑰茶很棒
But the White Rose tea was very soothing.
死  我真的勰  我要怎么C明
God damn it, I fucking love you! How do I prove that?!
去死吧
Go to hell!
你哪里都e想去
You're not goin' anywhere!
@是我的家
This is our home!
我缶了
I called the police!
我什么都告V他了
I told them everything.
他R上砹  @次他把你抓起
They're gonna come, and they're gonna lock you up this time.
不要再躲了  爸爸
There's no more hiding, Dad.
我...
I--
看看你ξ家庭都做了什么
Ohh, Look what you did to our family!
看看你都做了什么
Look what you did to it!
多么愚蠢
So stupid!
愚蠢
Stupid!
我可以解Q的
We can fix this.
不
Oh, no.
爸爸
Dad.
爸爸  不
Dad, no.
天啊
Aah! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
爸爸  住手
Dad, stop!
爸爸  你在干什么
Dad, what are you doing?!
住手
Stop!
爸爸  不要@
Dad, please don't do this.
拜托不要@
Please don't do this.
-@些是...  -爸爸  不要@么做
- I got these... - Dad, please don't do this.
你的生日T
...for your birthday candles.
住手  不要@幼
Stop. Please don't.
那死的
That goddamn necklace.
我撒e了
I lied!
我砭]有缶
I never called the police.
你]有
You didn't?
是的  我的
No. I made that up.
他不淼
They're not coming.
好  你很安全
Okay? You're safe.
你很安全
You're safe here.
H鄣
Oh, sweetheart.
你看上去真像你的
You look so much like your mother.
Σ黄  爸爸
I'm sorry, Daddy.
金伯利
Aah! Kimberly?!
我和你f了多少次得自己收拾
How many times have I told you to pick up after yourself?!
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
我今天
I'm having a...
^得非常非常糟心
just a really, really bad day.
我需要一些理解
I could use a little understanding here.
你是我的女
You're my daughter.
我互相照
We're supposed to look after each other.
你很明  力很大
You're a smart girl, lots of potential.
我知道我今天f了很多
I know I said a lot of things today and...
有些很人  我知道
some hurtful things. I know that.
但是M管如此
But through everything,
我是如此槟阕院
I have never been prouder of you.
你做得很好  H鄣
You've done so well, sweetheart.
你以前常躲在@里
You used to hide up here all the time.
很可
So cute.
我F在不躲了
I'm not hiding now.
碜ノ野
So come and get me.
@才乖嘛
That's my girl.
好
Okay.
操
Fuck!